{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "1&frasl;10 in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "0.1", "1.0", "0.01" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "<math><mfrac><mrow>3</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "3.0", "0.03", "0.3" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "<math>1<mfrac><mrow>7</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "1.7", "1.07", "1.77" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "<math>8<mfrac><mrow>9</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "9.8", "8.09", "8.9" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "<math>26<mfrac><mrow>5</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "2.56", "26.5", "26.05" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "<math><mfrac><mrow>18</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "1.8", "0.018", "0.18" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "<math><mfrac><mrow>27</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "0.27", "0.027", "2.7" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "<math><mfrac><mrow>428</mrow><mrow>100</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "0.428", "4.28", "0.0428" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "<math><mfrac><mrow>428</mrow><mrow>1000</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "0.428", "0.0428", "42.8" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "<math><mfrac><mrow>428</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "0.428", "4.28", "42.8" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "<math><mfrac><mrow>428</mrow><mrow>10000</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "0.428", "0.0428", "4.28" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "<math><mfrac><mrow>9</mrow><mrow>1000</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "0.0009", "0.009", "0.09" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "<math>27<mfrac><mrow>38</mrow><mrow>1000</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "27.038", "27.38", "27.0038" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "<math>27<mfrac><mrow>38</mrow><mrow>100</mrow></mfrac></math> in decimal form",
      "answers": [ "27.038", "27.38", "27.0038" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "Convert 2.05 into fraction",
      "answers": [ "<math>2<mfrac><mrow>5</mrow><mrow>100</mrow></mfrac></math>",
                   "<math>2<mfrac><mrow>5</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math>",
                   "<math>2<mfrac><mrow>5</mrow><mrow>100</mrow></mfrac></math>" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "Convert 28.45 into fraction",
      "answers": [ "<math>28<mfrac><mrow>45</mrow><mrow>1000</mrow></mfrac></math>",
                   "<math>28<mfrac><mrow>45</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math>",
                   "<math>28<mfrac><mrow>45</mrow><mrow>100</mrow></mfrac></math>" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "Convert 470.08 into fraction",
      "answers": [ "<math>47<mfrac><mrow>8</mrow><mrow>100</mrow></mfrac></math>",
                   "<math>470<mfrac><mrow>8</mrow><mrow>100</mrow></mfrac></math>",
                   "<math>470<mfrac><mrow>8</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math>" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "Convert 6.006 into fraction",
      "answers": [ "<math>6<mfrac><mrow>6</mrow><mrow>1000</mrow></mfrac></math>",
                   "<math>6<mfrac><mrow>6</mrow><mrow>100</mrow></mfrac></math>",
                   "<math>6<mfrac><mrow>6</mrow><mrow>10</mrow></mfrac></math>" ], "correct_answer": 1
    }

  ]
}

